Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): For 123 years, you've fought for working people all across this country. You've changed this nation, you've made this nation better, and I'm here today to say thank you for what
Speaker 2: you've done. There's no amount of profit that justifies the destruction of working families, that justifies destroying whole working communities. The big challenge we've got in the economy in America today is that too many of the people who run the megacorporations have forgotten right from wrong.
Speaker 2: I'm for the free market. I'm for free enterprise. I'm for capitalism. But above all, I am for right and wrong. And it is right to pay a working man what he deserves. It is right to fight for decent
Speaker 3: working conditions. It is right that you're treated as you deserve to be treated. And it's time we stood for what's right in America.
we need
Speaker 2: to protect workers we need to give workers rights over AI in the workplace we will not allow technology to replace workers in this country we'll make the technology work for us not the other way around this country is built on a promise that if you give a working person a shot and if you give him his liberty under God there's no telling what he can do the great American economy didn't just spring into being we had to build it more specifically you built it Teamsters built it
if the
Speaker 2: Teamsters are around and strong for another 123 years I bet America will be around as strong for another 250 God bless you God
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): bless the United States of America thank you for
having me here